Every week I make a video going through
people's websites and landing pages,
seeing
if I can give them advice.
If you wish to feature on one of these
videos, I'll be
as kind as possible,
and all you need to do
is click the link in the description,
and I'll add you to the list. Now,
to ensure that I'm not biased,
I've actually got
Declan, my videographer,
to pick these five candidates for me.
So let's begin with Josh K. Fay. Day job,
protect, plan, and grow
millions of pounds. Passion,
show how you can do it too.
Straight away with the bio, first place,
I just want to know what you do.
Personal finance.
Are we helping people make money?
Are we helping people save money?
Are we helping people invest money?
I think the fact
that I even have to ask
that question at this point goes to show
maybe that's something
we should put here. Now,
we don't need to double up on your name.
I literally can see it up here.
Well done getting your name on Instagram.
So instead, maybe a job title,
because I've just got your name again
and personal
finance, which doesn't particularly help.
Let's have a listen.
Money goals that will change your life.
Okay, love a carousel.
Probably say there's a bit too much text
here.
Let's say I'm scrolling,
just discovered your page. Oh,
he's done a carousel.
Going to have a look. Whoa,
that hurts my eyes because I'm old.
I'm going to have to actually squint a
bit.
One sentence probably per slide would be
enough.
What I'm looking to do every time I'm on
social media is I'm looking for a
reason to leave.
And by making this a little bit too long,
I want to leave.
There's a lot of information here.
I probably say too much.
That could probably be better off in an
email automation or some kind of lead
magnet. I just want to see a quote
that gets me thinking.
You know like that "Rich Dad,
Poor Dad" guy,
even though I think a lot of his
finance advice has been kind of
meticulously torn down.
When he says, "If you rent a house out
and you live in it,
it's a liability because
it loses you money, and it's an asset
if you don't live in it." That was like a
real short snippet
that I still remember years on.
That's what we're going to look for in
finance.
Look, this isn't about earning interest,
right?
It's not about optimizing your returns.
It's about breaking-
I've a feeling this
is maybe a clip from a longer form piece
of content.
But what you got to understand
is the first three seconds we
are looking to
establish what this is about.
Really in the first five to 10 seconds,
I want to
decide whether or not I'm going to watch
this.
Look, this isn't about earning interest.
I don't know what it's about.
Now, if this was its very own clip,
like say here, full video now on YouTube.
Credit card debt finance. Again,
I don't know how many more times you say
this.
The CEO of Instagram said
that hashtags don't do anything,
so stop putting them in
your bio.
It's about breaking that really horrible
cycle of paying off debt-
Okay, I still don't know what this
is about.
An issue here is,
I get it because I am guilty of this
myself, where I clip up long
form content, stick it on Instagram,
and maybe I don't care that much.
However,
the beginning of this just doesn't
establish what's happening.
Now,
you've gone to the attempt here of running
an A camera and a B camera, which
means I've got a camera there
and it's like having another camera here.
I haven't even gone to
that effort for this video.
If you care that much about being able to
clip your long form
content into short form,
you should script it and structure it
that way, that
you put 10 short form videos back to back,
and in essence, when you do your video,
ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, ba, bom,
you can then just clip it into those short
form pieces of content. And the issue
is because you haven't done that,
this just
doesn't really make sense.
And the way that you said right makes me
think it's not
scripted and it's freeboard.
And like you can see in my last video,
I'm all about
that. I just don't feel like this
is a very strong reel.
Your future self is counting on the
financial decisions you make today.
Bit cheesy. Going to throw it out there.
When it comes to really getting people
emotionally connected to their finances
for
thinking about their future,
I think we just need to look into things
like loss
aversion and negativity, and
if you really want, like for instance,
the majority of
people trying to lose fat aren't doing so,
so their future self will thank them.
They're doing it so they don't have a
fucking heart attack.
They're doing it so
that they don't collapse chasing their
kids around the garden.
And sometimes we do need to remind people
of that.
Do you still want to be renting in your
60s?
And it's not a bad thing to use negativity
in a bid to motivate people.
You know what's exhausting, right?
Having-
Starting a reel with right, which
is not going to get on. Right.
What is it Gary Economics says? Listen,
yeah.
There are some things you just shouldn't
say in content because it can damage
credibility. Sorry to say it,
Darren Cartel,
you say get me way too much.
Like you say an amazing sentence.
You'll be like, yeah,
and the philanthropic
nature of his ability to nonchalantly deal
with something was the problem. Get me.
I'm like, mate,
all the amazing stuff you just said,
you just killed by saying get
me. Anyway,
this just isn't working in my mind.
So let's say you have a long form content
and you bust out a really good YouTube
video.
Sometimes you just need to sit down
and do it again in 60 seconds.
So for instance, Declan
is going to take a clip now from my
Coke Zero video on YouTube
that did really well.
Sometimes you just fancy a nice cold can
of Coke Zero, and I know that there are
some geniuses on the internet that go,
"Just drink water." But what if you don't
fancy water and you want something cold
and fizzy to quench that thirst that you
had, so you find a can of Coke Zero?
If you think Diet Coke's better than Coke
Zero, you should leave the video now.
And now he's going to find a clip of it
when I did it as a short.
Sometimes you feel like a nice can of Coke
Zero, and just as you take a sip, your
auntie slaps it out of your hand and goes,
"Don't drink that.
It'll give you cancer."
When we finished recording
that amazing YouTube video, I
heard the beep on the camera. I said,
"Right.
Let's do it now in under 90 seconds."
And we did it all in under 90 seconds.
And that reel got millions
and millions of views,
grown by tens of thousands.
If what you're saying here, Josh,
is so amazing and helpful,
you should have done
your long format video,
looked at your scripts and gone, right,
let's make three
separate reels that can talk to these
points.
So for that bit,
what's the first thing you say here?
So you know what's exhausting, right?
Having three different credit cards.
So for that,
you should have got your wallet,
should have got three credit cards
out and going,
having three different credit cards
is really exhausting.
And let me tell you what you can do to
solve it. You've done the setup.
You've got the camera.
You've got the Shure SM7B.
You've got everything you need.
Is that even a little Cartier kettle I'm
seeing there, blood?
I don't think it would've been too
difficult for you to just make these short
form
reels. And props are great.
You could just hold them up like the
credit card.
A bit like this where I could say, hey,
if you want to download the anatomy of a
highly efficient sales page so
that you can get more conversions on your
website or
landing page,
just click the link in the description.
You see by having that little prop there,
I just have that little bit more
authority that I've just gone to
that little bit of effort to go down to
the store
and get that printed in A3.
There's a link in the description for
that, by the way.
That's a little bit of unagi.
What I've done there
is I've told you something at
the same time as plugging my own stuff.
You'll get used to that if you're new.
Feel like these should've been made to be
reels.
All right. It's Friday, and this week-
I hate content in the car. I
was guilty of doing this in like 2014,
2015. I know that your car
is your safe space.
It's just incredibly low effort,
and I would rather
that you're actually holding
your phone. When people,
I don't know what it is that,
I could be completely wrong
with this. I don't know what it
is about people having their phones in
their cars.
All right. It's Friday,
and this week a brand new client told me
that they had
loads of cash Stuffed under the mattress
I hate this. Okay? First of all,
you've used an annoying noise by saying,
"Right,
it's Friday. Don't care. This week,
a brand new client." There
are many ways to do
an appeal to authority. There
are many ways to show people
that you take on
clients,
but talking about your clients in your
setup, because your hook here is,
"Right, it's Friday." Probably give
that a one or a two out of 10.
But the setup,
"My client told me." The only thing worse
than would've been asking
for a follow-up before getting into the
video, and this hand is here because it's
ready to give you a slap.
I don't give a fuck about your client.
I don't give a fuck about
if they're new or not.
I don't give a fuck about the people you
work with.
All I give a fuck about
is my fucking finances. That's it.
And if I'm really brutally honest,
at this stage, I don't care about you.
However,
if you give me 10 to 15 bits of finance
information
that make me go, "Fucking hell,
I didn't know that," I'm going to really
start to
like you. The same way
that I can say Damien Talks Money
is really fucking good on
YouTube because he's helped me think, "Oh,
never thought of that." Jamie Roach,
accountant. Josh Thomas.
I'm naming people in the finance space,
not because I went
looking for them. I discovered them,
and I thought they were fantastic.
Don't talk about your fucking clients.
Simple as.
So for instance,
if you're going to use a client
testimonial, which I've done
recently, don't say,
"My client." Name them,
because then it becomes like a story.
For instance, I could say,
"Craig Jackson this week just went viral
on YouTube.
Craig Jackson just grew to 60,000
followers in the last
three months,
and Craig did it by following these
steps." Now, I don't have to say
they're my steps.
I don't have to say he's my student.
I just talk about that person,
because then you might go, "Well,
if Craig's done
it, I can do it." But when PT's,
"My client lost four kilograms,
and basically,
I got my client to..." Instead, you go,
"This is
Amanda. Amanda lost four kilograms,
and she managed to do it in only 10 weeks.
And the best part is,
she ate cereal every single day.
And in this video,
I'm going to tell you what you could do to
copy what Amanda did
and get the same results as Amanda.
And it may not even be cereal,
but there could be a food
that you love that you
could eat every day.
So let me explain how we did it." Good
news is, Josh, this
isn't going to be too hard to improve.
And I've got you quite early, 77 posts.
Right, so you have-
Starting sentences with right has got to
stop.
The very first thing you say in a video
is important.
I'm pretty sure for this one I said,
"Every week I critique people's content.
If you wish to get yours,
click the link in the description." That's
pretty
important because we get a lot of people
signing up for that.
The second you start with right-
That earning more money
is the secret to getting rich, right?
And it sort of makes sense. More income
equals more wealth.
But here's the thing that's going to shock
you.
I have worked with loads and loads
and loads of people earning
six figures and way more who've got less
money in the bank-
I think you might need to start scripting
using a teleprompter.
And I think that if you
were to write this,
you could do a lot better.
And maybe you should pose a question.
What if I was to tell you the secret to
accruing more wealth wasn't earning more
money? What if I was to tell you
that there are thousands of people out
there that
are using these three principles,
et cetera?
Now, an issue we're getting here
is I'm not sure if it's your hand hitting
the
table or if you're getting a pop filter
not doing its job here.
So in essence,
that Shure SM7B should be what they call a
chakras far
out, away from the mic.
If you wish to go closer like a Chris
Williamson,
you need to get the bigger pop filter
that's going to negate or get rid of that.
Now, if you're filming this yourself,
kudos. Great lighting.
Love that bit of Rembrandt,
bit of hair light in the back. Lovely.
But you should be running your audio
through some kind of audio processing.
There is a platform called Auphonic,
A-U-P-H-O-N-I-C, that
would get rid of the pops. Now,
for me here wearing headphones watching
this, it's
a problem for me.
And what's going to happen
is I've got really bad ADHD, and I'm
going to be concentrating on listening out
for the pops.
I'm not actually going to listen to
anything that you're saying.
The problem is not about how much you
earn,
okay? It's what happens to
that money once it hits your
account.
This will come with repetition.
I appreciate you're quite new to this.
And like I say, you're talking to camera,
you're putting yourself out there, you're
doing the reps.
You've got the good light
and the good audio.
You've done so much already.
We just need to really clean up what you
say.
We need to appreciate that
if this video is 13 minutes
and you could do it in
seven, do it in seven,
because what people want
is succinct information.
And I think that maybe an Elgato prompter,
one of these bad boys, and scripting
will really help you. Now,
I know I talk about him a lot.
Ed Lawrence is my sensei.
I've learned so much from YouTube from him
that I always recommend him.
He is a big fan of scripting.
I'm a bit more nuanced with my approach to
it,
but go watch some of his videos.
And this video he did recently
was very good.
But that doesn't mean
that you can't buy my stuff as well.
Only messing.
He does critiques as well.
The only reason I mention him so much is,
yeah, he's
great as well. I'm great. He's great.
We're great. Fine.
So we just got to work on this a little
bit. That's what I'm going to say.
We need to think about more strategically
what you say in the first few minutes.
Think of it this way. On a first date,
we make sure we look our best.
We make sure we smell good because we
are aware that if our first date does not
go
well, there'll be no more dates.
Same with this.
If your first three to five seconds
doesn't go well,
doesn't matter how big your
cock is later in the video. So Josh,
thanks for coming. Okay.
Obsession Car Detailing.
Let's give it a look. Do you know what?
I quite like car detailing as a niche.
I kind of was like, "Oh,
is it just washing your car?" It's like
washing your car
on steroids. And by the way,
if you're a man in the UK
and you want to check your
bloods,
I can hook you up with a blood test
through Manual, who I've invested into
recently.
I'll put a link in the description. Okay.
I like these images here.
What's that? A Porsche 911 992 GT3.
What a fantastic car. Okay.
Problem here. Paint protection,
ceramic coating, window tinting.
Because of that here,
we now have to expand to see the important
stuff
like a phone number,
how long you've been in business, and
when you're open.
So I wouldn't mind that being changed.
And also,
I think let's just delete all this.
You're in Canberra, right?
So let's just say Canberra's number one
car detailing company or something like
that. So the second people land there,
they're, "Oh, I live in Canberra.
I'll give this guy a go." Because it's
pretty obvious you do a lot of this stuff.
Bespoke detailing, window tinting.
You could even say then car detailing
and window tinting. Yeah.
But there's just too much here,
and this is what we call above the fold.
So I'm having to open the fold to get the
really important stuff, which just says
there's too much stuff up there.
What I'm seeing here is beautiful cars.
The problem I'm seeing here
is I don't know what they looked like
before.
So a before and after picture
is a story of some kind.
It becomes a story of a before
and after pretty much.
So if we could get this image maybe front
on, and we can have the car before and
after, you can then tell a story.
And the story is this
is what your car looks like
before. This is what it looks like after.
So just showing the finished product
is like just turning up to the end of a
film
when they win over the woman
and fall in love and go away together.
We don't see how bad it was before.
Hey, guys.
Welcome back to Obsession Car Detailing.
My name is Saad.
Okay. All of that, we just don't need.
"Hi, guys. Welcome back. Welcome.
This is Saad." I'm sorry, but don't care.
So like if we think of a car channel like
Carwow, "Hi, it's Matt Watson.
Today,
we're going to be here with four cars.
We're going to be doing a drag race
over..." It's what wins in a drag race
between
an Audi RS Q8 Performance,
a Lamborghini Urus.
Like straight away, the first thing
that comes out of his mouth is the hook.
What wins? You go, "Fuck,
I'm not even really sure." Well, today,
we're going into
the setup.
We've got an Audi RS Q8 Performance.
We've got a Lamborghini Urus.
We've got a BMW M5 Competition.
We've got this.
And we're going to find out which
is faster over the standing quarter mile.
Now, we've had the hook.
We've had the setup. "I'm Matt Watson.
Welcome to Carwow." Boom.
So I then in a Carwow video get to know
exactly
what it's about and what I'm going to get
before he mentions who it is.
So you could even be like,
"Is PPF really better than a vinyl wrap?"
Today we're going to go through stone
chips and scrapes on a vinyl wrap versus
PPF, and understand what is better
when it comes to protecting your car.
My name's Saad. This
is OBSSSSD Car Detailing.
So straightaway we've given someone the
respect and the opportunity to understand
whether or not they want to stay around
and watch the video, then we get into the
introduction.
We've done this the wrong way around.
And another quick video to show-
Don't need the music.
We just don't need it.
We can bring it in in a bit of time,
but not
What has been going on this past week.
First up, what is being on the M2.
Now, this car was in-
I don't know what it looked like before.
Hey, guys.
Welcome back to OBSSSSD Car Detailing.
My name is Saad.
You understand that this is a...
I've really got 61 likes on this.
It's kind of a bit of a waste of time.
[upbeat music]
So if I've never seen you before
and I come across your page,
I just don't know
what's happening.
And that's what people are doing.
They're swiping algorithms.
We need to capture their attention.
So the 911 is done,
ready to pick up.
Why is there no content of this before?
And the customer asked us to add these
really cool black-
Brother, get rid of the hashtags
... highlights here. I do believe
that you can have the OEM
PPF in black from factory.
What's this? This is a GTS, or
is it a Carrera?
911 Carrera, 911 GTS, whatever.
You could've said,
"Have you ever wondered why
there is a black plastic sticker here just
in front of the wheel arch?
Well, this is a 911 GTS Carrera,
and the issue is that these cars
use very grippy tires,
911 being one of the best performance cars
in the world.
And because of that reason,
having tires on this,
like Michelin Cup 2s, mean that
the tires can flick stones towards the
paintwork causing damage.
So what we've done on this car
is two things.
One,
we've PPF wrapped the entire car." Bring
the camera closer.
"If you can see here,
there's an invisible wrap on this
that protects the paint.
And if you're someone with a Porsche,
you might have seen this video." Then you
cut
to Matt Watson fixing
that orange GT3 RS that he did when he
crushed it at the Nürburgring.
And they peeled off the PPF,
and you realize that
the paint underneath
is completely untouched.
You go,
"So we've surrounded the car in that.
If you're interested in that,
there's a link in the description.
But second of all,
our customer has asked us to put a second
layer of PPF here
where stones are prone to chip at the
paintwork.
This usually comes OEM as clear,
but we've decided to step it up
and do it black.
What do you think? Does this look good?
Would you do this to your 911?" So do you
appreciate, no offense, how much
boring your version is
when people probably are curious.
Hey, guys.
Saad with OBSSSSD Car Detailing.
It's got to stop, Saad. It's got to stop.
All right, guys.
So we're detailing the interior of this
McLaren 720.
"All right, guys.
So we're interiorling the detail..."
If it's dirty or it's been
polished or whatever,
get your magic detailing stuff,
show me the
seat, do a stripe, and I'm going to go,
"Oh my God, look how much better the
leather looks now with Saad's just used
that bloody cleaning stuff on it.
It looks amazing.
I'm going to have to book into a local
detailer." Bro, give me
these cars. Give me your expertise.
Give me the fact that you can wrap PPF
and detail cars and do tinting.
Brother,
I'd have a million followers before the
end of the year.
This is such an interesting thing.
Bro, I follow five different pages
that do wraps.
I even did a video on the fact
that I'm thinking about investing into a
wrap
business thereby.
See something cool?
Damn. What happened, Kai?
Did you repaint this?
Nah, bro, just single step. Wow.
We've got to make this more compatible
with everyday people.
Brother,
do you know why Matt Watson gets millions
of people watching his videos?
Because people froth over cars.
They want to pretend it's theirs.
Remember we said everything is a story.
When they're seeing these cars,
they're imagining, "One day I'll have
that car.
I'll get it detailed." Most people don't
know what PPF is.
Most people don't know what detailing is.
Most people don't know how much a vinyl
wrap is or what it costs.
Most people don't know
that you can get a race PPF.
Most people don't know.
They just don't know. Your job
is to make people think, "Oh,
do you know what?
I found this company in Canberra,
and every time I watch one of their
videos, I'm
learning.
I didn't know." Teach me how to apply PPF.
Tell me why it takes several days.
Show me times it's saved a car, and
the amount of clients you're going to get
because, bro, you've got these sick cars.
What's that? A 718, a Ferrari. Bro,
I want to follow your page, but
I just need it more interesting, please.
Please.
And I can imagine you're probably getting
a bit of business through this, but not a
lot.
But if you just change this content up a
tiny bit, you're going to get so many
more views. And if 1 in 10,000 people
are ringing you up to bloody book in a
car,
you could triple the amount of views in a
few weeks.
Suddenly you're going to get triple the
amount of business.
This is worth tens of thousands of dollars
to you, bro. Yeah, a website's good.
You just want people to contact you.
By the time they clicked on the website,
they're going to be ready at that point
anyway,
but you're going to win them over on
socials.
Okay, we've got another one here.
Key Aesthetics.
Nurse-led aesthetic clinic.
Enhance your natural beauty, safety,
and profession. Swindon, Wiltshire.
Book your consultation today. Okay,
that's pretty good. Where do I book it?
Because if I click here,
it goes through to Facebook.
Some people don't have Facebook. Right?
I just don't.
I suppose they could always DM you.
Okay, if your name is Susanna Keylock,
let's change this to Susanna Keylock, and
let's change this to Susanna Keylock
because I want to feel and get to know
Susanna. I want to know what she's like.
And even here,
your five-star review isn't about your
services, it's about
you.
"I recently visited Susanna." They didn't
say, "I recently visited Key
Aesthetics." This is the biggest thing.
You need to start representing your brand.
And okay, we've got some good before
and afters. This is what we like to see.
And do you know what, Susanna?
I would probably like to see you coming
forward and
representing this a little bit.
I'm not mad into the old Botox,
lip filler stuff personally.
But by showcasing some of this stuff.
I think also you might need to start
playing into doing some Reels.
So Reels are favorited into the algorithm,
so you're going to have to start making
some video content.
You can still use these photos,
and you could even be in frame.
You could put this behind you and say,
"As you can see up here,
we've got some skin
that had some issues, and what we did
is we put a bit of Botox,
and it looks like
this. Some people think that Botox
is dangerous." Give some facts.
"Some people think it's really expensive."
Give some facts.
"Some people say it's really bad." Give
some facts.
If you want to book in,
use the link in the bio.
Because none of these
are getting shown to Explore because
you're not making them
as Reels. So if we could start doing that,
that'd be lovely.
And maybe let's take some of your results
and make it a carousel.
If you add some audio to the carousel,
it'll probably get shown in the Explore
feed. Thank you for coming.
That's what she said.
Freshly Baked Fight Wear. Hmm. Okay. Okay.
I don't like this underscore, but anyway.
Freshly baked, highly flavored,
limited runs, no restocks.
Has this got a connotation with smoking
weed? Don't know. I like the design.
It's pretty cool
Okay. I suppose it's difficult, right?
People do make jujitsu clothing.
It's a hard industry
because people don't need
that many rash guards.
They last a very long time.
The majority of the quality is very good.
A lot of jujitsu athletes are poor,
so they want big sponsorships, so it
becomes expensive. You think,
let's say a jujitsu athlete wants
£500 a month,
and you make £5 a rash guard.
You've got to sell 100 rash guards a month
just to cover the cost of your flipping
athlete. So it's very difficult.
What I would say is missing here
is what is this brand about?
What does Freshly Bake mean?
What does it stand for? Are you a charity?
Do you do anything?
Do you give back? Okay, this
is the just question I pose you.
Why should I buy your shit
and not someone else's?
I would like you to comment
that below the video, please. Next.
Okay, drink Amavoi. Let's get into it.
Let's go.
All right,
we've got a conflict of interest.
If it ain't Nutonic,
we ain't talking about it. Okay,
Amavoi Drinks Company.
Bold botanicals made in the UK.
I quite like that, if I'm honest.
Okay, we're going to see...
Can you shut the fuck up whistling?
I've got two more minutes to this video.
You're pissing me off.
Got a mate staring at me.
Just think fucking whistling his way.
All right.
I like the design of this can.
Tarragon and mint. I like that.
Bit of guerrilla marketing. Okay,
so the one thing that I'd
want to know from this,
we have the biggest,
the similar kind of things with
Nutonic is people want to know,
where does this fit in?
Do I mix it with gin?
Do I have it in the morning?
What does it do for me?
Does it have caffeine in it?
What's the purpose of this drink?
Is it to just be refreshing?
I've got a lot of questions.
So like the can,
botanical citrus sparkle.
What does botanical mean?
It comes from plants.
I
would love for this to say soda, seltzer,
energy drink, productivity drink,
probiotic. Is it a probiotic?
Because then you can move into
that realm with like
Poppy. Yeah,
I'm struggling to understand what this is.
Bold botanicals.
I'm pretty sure with Nutonic we say the
world's number
one productivity drink. Yeah,
so it's like world's number one
productivity drink.
Oh, cool,
this drink will make me productive.
Research-backed ingredients.
Oh, cool. Improve your focus
and attention. Available on Amazon.
So we're just missing a bit of that,
if I'm honest.
Let's see if your website has it. Oh,
this looks great, mate.
Look, the fucking can looks amazing.
I like the colors.
I like this layout. Bro, I tell you what,
you don't really need the
highly effective anatomy of a sales page.
You don't need that link in the
description because this looks great.
Like spot and blend brews plants
are herbal freshness. Okay, freshness.
So are we looking at hydration?
I want to know the purpose of the drink a
little
bit more. I want to try it.
If you're happy to send me some, email me
james@nutonic.com.
I'm going to be at home in the UK next
week, and I would love to
try it. Yeah, that's what I feel
is missing with this. What's your why?
What does it do, brother?
I'm excited to try it.
If you want to feature in one of these
videos and get some brutally honest
feedback,
that link's going to be there in the
description.
Going to have the other link for the
anatomy of a highly efficient sales page,
and
the third link will be
if you want to work with me.
As you can see here, oh,
I've been pretty on it today.
We have threads of all different people
working with each other.
Even here,
we're going through some trial reels.
This is where people can kind of share
their wins of progress they're making with
them,
although they've changed some of that.
As you can see,
I'm very active in helping people get new
leads, retain new
clients, whatever it is.
So once this video goes off to Declan for
the edit, I'm
going to spend the rest of my afternoon
here helping people.
If you found this video helpful,
click the link in the description.
If you don't want to click any of the
links in the description,
fear not,
the boffins at YouTube have recommended
this video here, and they reckon
you're going to love it.
If you enjoyed this one,
you'll love this one. Bye-bye.